{
    "id": "c7604423b40343989c01586d381ed5d6",
    "title": "Active And Passive Voice Exercise",
    "questions": [
        {
            "question": "John won the first prize. / The first prize .................. by John.",
            "description": "",
            "answers": [
                "won",
                "was won",
                "has won",
                "had won"
            ],
            "correct": 1,
            "id": "7ecd6101ab0f4571b0f6723a0b1928c5"
        },
        {
            "question": "They have appointed them as their monitor. / He ....................... their monitor.",
            "description": "",
            "answers": [
                "has appointed",
                "has been appointed",
                "have been appointed"
            ],
            "correct": 1,
            "id": "b5add1c0421f4cc19bd4e69e22535216"
        },
        {
            "question": "She has written two books. / Two books .................. by her.",
            "description": "",
            "answers": [
                "are written",
                "have been written",
                "have written"
            ],
            "correct": 1,
            "id": "63aa13cba5914e60aab32046ac79c5aa"
        },
        {
            "question": "I sent the parcel in the morning. / The parcel .......................... in the morning.",
            "description": "",
            "answers": [
                "was sent",
                "had been sent",
                "has been sent"
            ],
            "correct": 0,
            "id": "25dae1c4dfd9430a8809bef57592165b"
        },
        {
            "question": "They made the boy drink the milk. / The boy .................. to drink the milk.",
            "description": "",
            "answers": [
                "has made",
                "was made",
                "had been made"
            ],
            "correct": 1,
            "id": "ac875d35c52445e582e374fd0fa7fd38"
        },
        {
            "question": "They asked him to wait. / He ........................ to wait.",
            "description": "",
            "answers": [
                "has asked",
                "had asked",
                "was asked"
            ],
            "correct": 2,
            "id": "fc0d40f3c0a440f1b2bfca27962dc60c"
        },
        {
            "question": "They have invited me to their party. / I ..................... to their party.",
            "description": "",
            "answers": [
                "have invited",
                "have been invited",
                "had been invited"
            ],
            "correct": 1,
            "id": "88fbe25a68764d9abfcf57dcb03a2d57"
        },
        {
            "question": "They have called off their wedding. / Their wedding ................. called off.",
            "description": "",
            "answers": [
                "has been",
                "have been",
                "had been"
            ],
            "correct": 0,
            "id": "b827848754244414a9aeb98d66f9881c"
        },
        {
            "question": "Positive hydrogen atoms attract negative oxygen atoms. / Negative hydrogen atoms ...................... to positive hydrogen atoms.",
            "description": "",
            "answers": [
                "attracted",
                "are attracted",
                "have attracted"
            ],
            "correct": 1,
            "id": "8d957bcb9cf74605add4e400cb87baf9"
        },
        {
            "question": "They took the child to the doctor. / The child ...................... to the doctor.",
            "description": "",
            "answers": [
                "took",
                "has taken",
                "had taken",
                "was taken"
            ],
            "correct": 3,
            "id": "27380962416f4045b4013b141175594d"
        },
        {
            "question": "The abductors tortured the boy. / The boy ...................... by the abductors.",
            "description": "",
            "answers": [
                "has tortured",
                "was tortured",
                "had tortured"
            ],
            "correct": 1,
            "id": "e9241918e3914497b9fc28ebeb9ae7b0"
        },
        {
            "question": "They hanged the criminal. / The criminal ...................... by them.",
            "description": "",
            "answers": [
                "has hanged",
                "was hanged",
                "had hanged"
            ],
            "correct": 1,
            "id": "b8c37c06f8fc41f1bddd80da30d29a93"
        },
        {
            "question": "The masons are building the house. / The house ........................ by the masons.",
            "description": "",
            "answers": [
                "is built",
                "is being built",
                "has been building"
            ],
            "correct": 1,
            "id": "f36fc066cfda4a1fb2c19cdd0b836913"
        }
    ]
}